吼吼吼 谁不想去
Ho ho ho, who wouldn't go?
在屋顶上踢踢踢
Up on the housetop click click click.
和圣诞尼克一起穿过烟囱
Down through the chimney with good Saint Nick.
[Squeals]
珍妮，太棒了
Jenny, that was so great.
你的表扬对我意义重大 丽芙
That means everything coming from you, Liv.
有了这首对唱和丽芙的独唱
Well between this duet and Liv's solo,
这将是最棒的点亮圣诞树仪式
this is going to be the best tree lighting ceremony ever.
哦 谢谢你优美的长笛演奏 鲁尼女士
Oh, thank you, Mrs. Rooney, for your wonderful flute playing.
就像听到了美丽和优雅拥抱
It's like listening to beauty share a hug with Grace.
谢谢你 珍妮
Well, thank you, Jenny.
你知道 我在高中掌握三样事物
You know, I was a bit of a triple threat in high school myself.
长笛 指挥棒和加油旗
Flute, baton twirling, and flag spinning.
啦啦队在这里（Pep squad代指啦啦队）
Pep squad in the house.
一旦你会操纵加油旗
Once you've mastered the flag twirl...
你会永远铭记
You never forget.
就像刻在骨子里了
It's in my bones.
好了 我要去看看晚餐了
Well, I'm gonna go check on dinner.
你们继续练习吧 听起来很棒
Now you girls keep practicing. You sound great.
额 每个人听起来都很棒当他们和丽芙一起唱的时候
Aw. Everyone sounds great when they're singing with Liv.
因为你听起来个垂死的海象
Because you sound like a dying walrus.
你太会说话了
You are just too sweet.
等等 什么
Wait, what?
听着 金发妞
Listen up, blondie.
我要从这个愚蠢的外套上做些改变
I'm making some changes starting with this stupid outfit.
我是这场演出的明星 我应该有很酷的衣服
I'm the star of the show. I should have the cool dress!
额
Um...
我很确定我才是演出的明星 我是那个要点亮树的人
I'm pretty sure I'm the star of the show. I am the one lighting the tree,
哦 我也是曾经有自己的受欢迎的电视节目的人
oh, and also I'm the one who had her own hit TV show.
如果你试图抢走我的光环 我将把你嚼碎了并吐出去
If you try to steal my spotlight, I will chew you up and spit you out.
鲁尼女士
Mrs. Rooney.
你能送我回家么 我答应妈妈要给祖父读书的
Could you drive me home? I promised Mommy I'd read to grandpa tonight.
好吧 你好的不真实
Well, you are just too good to be true.
好的 我正要去买些东西做晚餐 一块走吧
Sure, I was just gonna get some things for dinner. Let's go.
我得先拥抱一下丽芙
Not before I get a hug from Liv.
注意你身后
Watch your back.